<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MBeliou</title>
    <link>https://MBeliou.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MBeliou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 14:07:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://MBeliou.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ionic Vue in 5 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/ionic-vue-in-5-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 14:07:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/ionic-vue-in-5-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Since my article on VueJs, curiosity has brought me to look for a way to develop a mobile application with it.
After spending some time googling around and playing with a few frameworks, I ended up finding out about the release of Ionic 4 and it&amp;rsquo;s newfound support for Vue.
Why choose Ionic? Ionic has been around since 2013 and helps you build hybrid mobile apps using web technologies, which simply means that after writing the app once, it will be deployable across Web, Android, IOS and Electron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Chose Vuejs For All My Projects</title>
      <link>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/why-i-chose-vuejs-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 19:02:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/why-i-chose-vuejs-projects/</guid>
      <description>Coming to Javascript from other languages such as Python and Golang, I was a bit overwhelmed by the bad press it was getting, both from its well known gotchas and from the amount of ever-changing frameworks in existence.
I started out learning vanilla JS and JQuery from w3schools and the Eloquent Javascript book (Here&amp;rsquo;s the online version of it), which gave me a fair understanding of the language but a somewhat shaky foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Mining - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/cryptocurrency-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 15:59:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/cryptocurrency-mining/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize over the last year that people get quite curious about cryptocurrency mining and have had several people coming to me ask about how it works and if running a mining operation is feasible.
In what will most likely be a series of post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain what mining actually is and how you can take part in it.
What is mining? Every cryptocurrency needs a way to assert the legitimacy of the transactions occurring through its network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Bitcoin Options</title>
      <link>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/understanding-bitcoin-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:36:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MBeliou.github.io/posts/understanding-bitcoin-options/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin is a volatile asset that has grown exponentially ever since its inception in 2009. Being essentially unregulated, it has found immense popularity with people mostly unprepared to deal with both its 2017&amp;rsquo;s quick rise and 2018&amp;rsquo;s disastrous fall.
This post is meant to explain what options are and how they can be used to protect your value and lock-in profits without giving up on a possible upside.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>